Which involves, effectively in short, transplanting an exterior wall in an existing building
そのなかで、短期間で効率的に、特に決まっていない場所からブロックを一つずつ運んで、
from a site yet to be determined, brick by brick, here to the mill.
既存の建築物の外壁を移動させるような事もやっているわ。
It just so happened that there's a demolition 	happening right now down the street from here.
ここからこの道をずっと行ったところで、まさに今取り壊しが行われている。
And I've been observing and documenting the	demolition.
私は取り壊しをずっと観察してドキュメントを作っているの。
They're doing it all with machines,
because it's quite a big building.
その建物はとても大きいので、取り壊しは全て重機で行われているわ
I've just been asking the guys about,
you know, demolition and how to do it,
そこの人たちから、取り壊しについてと、どうやって取り壊しているのかという事について聞き取りをしているのよ。
and it turns out that this company has been responsible for a lot of the demolition in
それでこの会社が、多くの取り壊しに関しての責任をもっているという事が分かった。
Manchester over the last thirty years.
ここ30年間のマンチェスターで行われいてる取り壊しに関してね。
And I think this is partially why this project as well.
それで私は部分的にだけど、これがこのプロジェクトの理由だと思った。
They seem to have this policy of trying to create	a new future by razing.
彼らは取り壊す事で新しい未来を創造する、というポリシーを持っているように見える。
But it's about the spectacle of change, and they want people to feel like change is happening,
だけどそれは変化のスペクタクルの部分について言っていて、そして彼らは人々には、変化が偶然発生しているように感じて欲しいと思っている。
but they don't actually have any real plans for	what's going to happen to that site yet.
けれど彼らはその場所で何が起こるのかについて、何の具体的なプランも実際には持ってないの。
It's mainly about the internet, I guess.
主にインターネットに関する事だと思う。
And the way that you sort of have this kind of divorced relationship from history.
そこでは関係が歴史から切り離されている。
And I was looking at the legacy of the club scene here, which is a bit of a strange thing,
それで私はここでクラブシーンの現状（なれの果て？残骸？）を見てたの。少し変な事だけど、
and sort of what's happening now in terms of kids who are a generation younger than I am.
今ここの、私より若い世代の子供達に起こっている事をね。
And their relationship to things.
また彼らの物事の間の関係の作り方をね。
It kind of was this leveling process with me, as someone who's not from here,
これは私にとっての、この土地の出身でないものとしての対等になるためのプロセスなんだけど、
and didn't grow up with it, and has a very, quite different background but sort of similar interests.
この環境で育ってない者として、そして本当に異なったバックグラウンドをもち、けれども同様の興味を持つ者として。
I'm kind of excited for how you can access a level playing field, something that happens through
どうやって公平な場所にアクセスできるかは、ある種エキサイティングな感覚があるわ。インターネットを通じて発生するような場所ね。
the internet that, you know, like maybe me and these kids have an equal access,
そこでは子供達とは同じようにアクセスできる。
which is also kind of one that's also very devoid.
そしてその場所は同時に、とても欠落してもいるわ。
If it's taking that building and then trying to just, you know, take it out of time,
もしもその作業が、ただ、そのビルを時間から取り除いて、
and then make a kind of imprint of it somewhere else,
それで、どこか別の場所に刻み込むなら、
but if it is just of bricks then it kind of comes back all apart again.
でも、それがただのブロックで、またばらばらになってしまうなら、
It's just about carving out a moment, kind of like a　photograph almost.
それはただ瞬間を彫刻することであって、なんというか、ほぼ写真のようなものね。